Guide to the Stanford Historical Photograph Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Stanford Family Photographs, Series 2
  - Central Pacific--Private Car (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Photograph of the the railroad, and a sign that reads, 10 miles of Track, laid I one day. April 28th 1869., 1869 Jan. 20
      Caption Reads: Near Promontory Point, Utah.
  - Golden Gate Woolen Mills (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Photograph of an steamship., 1867 Nov. 27
    - Photograph of a Occidental and Oriental Steamship Co. ship., 1971 June
    - Photograph of a steamship., 1971 June
    - Photograph of two steamships side-by-side., 1971 June
    - Photograph of a steamship and observers., 1971 June
    - Photograph of a steamship docking., 1871 June
  - Occidental and Oriental Steamship Co.--Fol.1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Photograph of an advertisment for the Occidnetal and Oriental Steamship Co. which was transporting people to Japan and China., 1971 June
      Caption Reads: Occidental & Oriental Steamship Company. For Japan and China leave wharph, Cor. First an Brannan STS., at noon, for Yokohama and Hongkong. Passage Tickets Cabin plans on Exhibition and Passage Tickets for Sale at C.P.R.R. Company General Offices
    - Advertisement for Occidental and Oriental Steamships traveling between San Francisco, Hawaiian Islands, Japan, China, India, & Australasia., 1871 June
      Caption Reads: Between San Francisco, Hawaiian Islands, Japan, China, India, & Australasia VIA - Occidental & Oriental S.S. Co. San Francisco, CAL.
    - Photograph of a steamship in the distance with four other row boats floating around it., 1871 June
      Caption Reads: S.S. Forie.
    - Photograph of one steamship and two other ships., 1871 June
  - Occidental and Oriental Steamship Co.--Fol.2 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Spring Valley Waterworks (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Bros. Oil Interests (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Carriages and Coachmen (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Stanford Carriages and Coachmen--Muybridge (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Biographical Photographs, Series 3
  Photographs of individual faculty, trustees, and staff, with a few prominent alumni represented.
  - Abbott, Nathan (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abramowitz, Moses (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Leroy (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acrivos, Andreas (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Dwight (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Adams, Ephraim D. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adams, Frank (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Maxwell (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Addis, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alabaster, Lewis P. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alden (possibly Raymond MacDonald Alden) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aldrich, Putnam (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alexander, Wallace McK. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allan, Evelyn Wight (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Allanson, Bertram (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Allardice, Robert E. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Anita (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Ben S. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Col. Harry B. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Allen, J. Knight (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Allen, Peter C. (and Mrs.) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Warren D. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Allen, Yolanda (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Alley, Wayne E. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Allin, Cephas D. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Allyn, Nathaniel (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Almond, Gabriel (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Almond, Nina (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ambrose, Arthur W. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ames, Elsa Lovina (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Anderson, Frank (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Anderson, Frederick "Fritz" (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Anderson, Martin (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Anderson, Melville Best (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Anderson, Melville Best--Family Members (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Anderson, Ross F. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Andreen, Harry Mayo (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Andrews, Asa A. ("Uncle John") (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Angel, Frank (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arbuckle, Ernest C. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Arnold, David L. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Arnold, John E. (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Arnold, Ralph (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Augsberger, Robert (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Aupperle, Harold W. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ayer, Fred C. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ayer, William E. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Babcock, William (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bach, George Leland (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Bacon, Harold M. (and Mrs.) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Baez, Albert (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Baez, Joan (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Baganoff, Donald (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bahney, Luther W. (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Bailey, Margery (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Bailey, Thomas A. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Baker, Shirley (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Balch, Richard (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ball, Robert (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Ballard, Carl M. (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Bannister, L. Ward (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Barber, James L. (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Barber, Robert F. (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Barber, W.M.B. (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Barclay, Thomas S. (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Bark, William C. (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Barkan, Adolph (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Barker, Chester (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Barnes, Earl (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Barnes, Mary Sheldon (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Barnett, George de Forest (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Barnhisel, Arthur H. (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Barnhisel, [Claire] Grace (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Barr, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Barrett, Richard W. (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bartky, A. John (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Bassett, Lee Emerson (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bates, David (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bavelas, Alex (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Beadle, George (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Beard, Paul J. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Beardsley, Charles A. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Beatty, Herbert I. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Beaver, William L. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Behrens, Earl C. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Belcher, Frank B. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bell, Reginald (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bender, Albert (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bentley, Rufus C. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Berendsoen, Lloyd H. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Berg, Paul (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Berger, Alice (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bergstrom, Francis W. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bergstrom, John (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bergstrom, John--Family Members (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Berlin, Mrs. Charles E. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Berner, Bertha (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Berry, Stillman (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bershader, Daniel (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Beurhaus, George (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bevier, George (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Beyers, Robert W. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bing, Peter S. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Birchard, Quentin R. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Birkmeyer, Karl (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Blackman, Chester W. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Blackwelder, Eliot (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Blake, Sidney Fay (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Blanchett, Herbert (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Blattner, Helene (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Blichfeldt, Hans Frederik (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Blinks, Lawrence R. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bloch, Felix (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Blodgett, Benjamin C. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Blois, Richard M. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bloomfield, Arthur L. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Boalt, Gilbert D. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Boezinger, Bruno (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Boggs, Theodore H. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bohart, George S. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bolin, Rolf (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bonner, Charles W. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Boothe, Peggy (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Boris, Kosta (and Mrs.) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Botsford, David M., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bowman, Guy C. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Boxmeyer, Charles H. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Boyd, Harper W. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Boyd, Walter H. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Bracewell, Ronald N. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Bradley, Mrs. Ethel L. and George A. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bradley, Harold W. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bradley, Oliver U. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Brand, Carl (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Brandin, Alf E. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Brandsten, Ernst M. "Ernie" (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Brandt, Karl (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Branner, George C. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Branner, John Casper--Inauguration (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Branner, John Casper--Portraits--Fol.1 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Branner, John Casper--Portraits--Fol.2 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Branner, John Casper (and Mrs.)--with others (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Branner, John K. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Brasch, Frederick E. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Brauman, John I. (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Brem, Lorna (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Briggs, R.S. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Briggs, William O. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Brigham, William (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Britton, William (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Broderick, Richard G. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Brooker, Charles F. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brooks, E. Howard (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Anna Louisa (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Bolton Coit (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Brown, Charles H. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Brown, D.E. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Elva Fay (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Brown, Joseph Grant (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brown, Leland H. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Brown, Philip (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Robert McAfee (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Brown, Robert Minge (and Mrs.?) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brown, Walter H. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Brun, Samuel J. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bryan, Barnabas (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bryan, Richard (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bube, Richard H. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Buck, Alice Meyer (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Buck, Philip W. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Buck, Rufus (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Buckel, C. Annette (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Buckingham, Elisabeth Lee (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Buelna, Antonio (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bull, Jacqueline M. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bullock, Charles J. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Buma, Maurine (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bunn, John (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bunnell, John (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Burbank, Luther (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Burdick, Charle K. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Burke, William E. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Burlingame, Leonas L. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Burnham, Marie S. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Burrows, Fred G. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bush, Chilton R. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Buss, Claude (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Butler, Robert M. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Byram, Adrian C. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Byrd, Oliver (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Byrne, James W. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Cahoon, John F. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Calderwood, Jack (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Calhoun, Scott (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Campbell, Douglas Houghton--Fol.1 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Campbell, Douglas Houghton--Fol.2 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Campbell, Robert W. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Campbell, W. Glenn (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Cannon, Henry Lewin (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Cannon, W.M. Austin (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Caperon, Paulin (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Carlson, Donald T. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Carman, Albert P. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Carnochan, W. Bliss (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Carpenter, Thomas (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Carr, William Herbert (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Carroll, Joseph S. (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Carruth, William Herbert (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Carson, W. W. (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Carter, Ann (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Cathcart, Arthur M. (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Cerf, Lawrence D. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Chambers, Jack V. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Chan, Shao Wing (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Chandler, Harry (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Chandler, Loren R. (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Chandler, Robert (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Chang, I-Dee (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Chapin, Leland T. (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Charles, Caroline M. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Chase, Robert M. (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chavalas, Gus J. (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Christensen, Kenneth C. (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Christopher, Warren (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Chubb, John (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Claerbout, Jon F. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Clark, Arthur B. (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Clark, Birge (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Clark, Frederick C. (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Clark, George A. (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Clark, George T. (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Clebsch, William A. (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Clevenger, Galen H. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Clever, Linda Hawes (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Cochran, Guy (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Code, Thomas K. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Coffin, Charles A. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Coffis, James T. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cohn, Roy B. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Coladarci, Arthur P. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Frank (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cole, Wendell (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Coleman, S. Waldo (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Colliver, John (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Comstock, John Henry--Comstock, Anna B. (Mrs. John Henry) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Concannon, George R. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Congdon, Edgar D. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Conrad, (Gaylord) Kent (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Converse, E.C. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Cooley, A. Crawford (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Coolidge, Dane (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Cooper, William Alpha (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Cooper, William Alpha--Family Members (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Cooper, William Alpha--Family Members (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cooper, William S. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Cootner, Paul (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Coover, John E. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Coffis, James T. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Corbin, Alain (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Corbus, William (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Cordry, Thomas W. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cory, Henry M. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Cory, Mabel Hyde (?) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Cotton, Thomas A. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Cottrell, Edwin A. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Coutts, Peter (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Coutts, Peter--Family (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Cowden, William (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cowley, William H. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Cox, Charles E. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Craig, Gordon A. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Crandall, Roderic (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Cranston, Alan (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Crary, Charles J. ("Jud") (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Crawford, Albert C. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Creger, William P. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Creighton, Kenneth D. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Creveling, Louis (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Crocker, Charles (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Crocker, Charles Frederick (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Crocker, Mrs. Clea (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Crocker, Mrs. Henry (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Cronenwett, Paul H. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Crook, Welton J. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Cross, Charles N. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Cross, Helen Green (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Crothers, Goerge E. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Cubberley, Ellwood P.--Fol.1 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Cubberley, Ellwood P.--Fol.2 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Cubberley, Ellwood P.--Fol.3--Mrs. C. Campus Residence--Groups (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Culver, George B. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Culver, George B.--with Family Members (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Culver, George Bliss, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Culver, Louise (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Culver, Richard K. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cuthbertson, Kenneth M. (and Mrs.) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cutler, Leland W. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Daley, Katherine F. ("Kay") (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Danforth, Charles H. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dantzig, George B. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Darrah, Estelle M. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Darrow, Karl K. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Dart, [Sibyl] Louise (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Davidson, F.J.A. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Davidson, Percy E. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Davidson, William R. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Daves, Delmer L. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Burt L., Jr. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Davis, Douglas D. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Horace (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Marvin C. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Paul H. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Robert T. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Day, A. Grove (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Dazey, Kendal I. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - De Debra, Daniel B. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - DeForest, Jean L. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - DeForest, Lee (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - DeGrazia, Alfred (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - DeLeeuw, Karel (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - DeLemos, Pedro J. (fomerly Lemos) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Deming, Daisy (Margaret) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - De Pew, Chauncey (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Dey, Benjamin C. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Dickson, Ernest C. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Diehm, Walter (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Diggles, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Dils, Eugene W. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Dinkelspiel, Lloyd W. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Djerassi, Carl (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Doane, Rennie Wilbur (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dodds, Henry G. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Dodds, John W. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Dodge, Melvin Gilbert (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dofflemyer, Robert (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Dole, Kenneth (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Domonoske, Arthur B. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Dornbusch, Sanford (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Dougall, Herbert E. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Douglass, Earl S. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Downing, Paul M. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Doyle, Anastasia (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Doyle, John T.--[Possible Views of Menlo Park Home] (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Doyle, Morris M. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Drake, Noah Fields (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Drew, Elmer Reginald (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Driscoll, Richard K. (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Du Bridge, Lee A. (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Ducommon, Charles E. (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Dudley, Ernest G. (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Dudley, William R. (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Duffus, Robert L. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Duffy, Philip G. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Dulley, Frederick L. (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Duniway, Clyde A. (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Duniway, Ben C. (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Dunn, Donald A. (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Dunn, Orrin W. (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Durand, William F. (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Durrell, Carl E. (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Dushane, Graham P. (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Dyke, Estelle Darrah (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Dykstra, Clarence A. (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Earhart, Amelia (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Eastman, Benjamin B. "Ben" (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Eaton, Louis H. (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Eaton, Orrison U. (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Eberle, William D. (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Eckart, William R. (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Eden, Col. John R. (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Edison, Thomas A.--(visit at Stanford) (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Edwards, Ada (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Edwards, Paul C. (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Ehrlich, Paul (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Eliassen, Rolf (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Eliel, Paul (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Eliot, Charles W. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Elliott, Harold F. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Elliott, Orrin Leslie (and Family) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Elmore, Jefferson (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Eloesser, Leo (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Elwell, Cyril Frank (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Elwell, Cyril Frank--Instruments fol. 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Elwell, Cyril Frank--Instruments fol. 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Ely, Northcutt (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Endsley, Daniel S.--Endsley, Mrs. Daniel S. (Sue Tolnay) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Erb, Donald (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Erb, William M. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Errera, Alfred (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Erwin, Ernest S. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Eshleman, Von R. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio M., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio M., Sr. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Eurich, Alvin C. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Evans, Luther H. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Evermann, Barton W. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fagan, Elmer D. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fagerburger, Dixon, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fairbank, William M. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fairclough, Henry Rushton--#1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fairclough, Henry Rushton--#2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fairman, Charles (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Farmer, Edward M. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Farmer, Elmer E. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Faught, William S. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Faulkner, Ray N. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Faust, Clarence H. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Fay, Charles W. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Fay, Sidney (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fehrenbacher, Don E. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Fergusson, James G. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Ferris, Gordon F. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Ferziger, Joel H. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Fesler, Bert (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fickert, Charles M. (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Field, Charles K. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Field, Joey Y. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Field, Lester M. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Fielder, Ortha Belle (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Fish, Carlton R. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Fish, J. C. L. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Fisher, Harold H. (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Fisher, Walter Kenrick (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Fitzgerald, James T. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Flory, Paul J. (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Flugel, Ewald (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Folsom, Myron A. (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Fondahl, John W. (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Fong, Herbert (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Ford, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Foster, Benjamin Oliver (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Fowler, W. H. B. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Frankenheimer, Julius (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Franklin, Edward Curtis (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Franklin, H. Bruce (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Franklin, Marc A. (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Frantz, Harry W. (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Franzini, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Frasier, George W. (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Freelen, Robert (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Freeman, Lewis R. (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Friedel, Frank (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Friedman, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Fuller, W. Parmer, Jr. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Fuller, W. Parmer III (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Furman, Nathaniel H. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gable, Robert (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Gale, Horace Bigelow (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Galligan, David M. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Gamble, Ivette (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gange, John F. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Garber, John (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gardiner, Gertrude (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gardner, D. Charles (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Gardner, John W. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Garfias, Valentine R. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Garwood, Christopher (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gay, Edwin (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Geary, William D. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Geddes, Gail (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Geier, Leo (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - George, Arthur T. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gerbode, Frank (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Germane, Charlotte (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Gibbons, Beulah (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Gibbs, James L., Jr. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gibson, Count O. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Gibson, Weldon B. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Giese, Arthur (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Gilbert, Charles H. (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Gilman, Philip K. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Ginzton, Edward L. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Gladwyn, Lord (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Glascock, William L. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Glaser, Robert J. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Gleim, Edgar M. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Glenn, Barbara (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Glover, Frederic O. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Goebel, Julius (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Goheen, John D. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Golder, Frank (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Goldstein, Auram (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Gonda, Thomas A. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Good, Edwin A. (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Goodan, May Chandler (Mrs. Roger) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Gordon, George (and family) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Gore, Arthur (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Grant, Eugene L. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Grant, John E. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Grant, U. S. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Grass, Donald F. (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Gray, Agnes (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Gray, H. D. (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Grayson, Robert H. "Bobby" (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Green, Cecil H. (and Mrs.) (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Green, Rufus Lot (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Greene, C. W. (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Gregg, Robert C. (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Gregory, Thomas T. C. (and Mrs.) (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Grey, John R. (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Grieder, Elmer M. (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Griffin, James O. (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Griffith, Wayland C. (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Griggs, Edward H. (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Grismore, Grover C. (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Gros, Robert M. (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Gross, Richard E. (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Grosso, Domingo (The Hermit) #1 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Grosso, Domingo (The Hermit) #2 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Gruwell, Robert W. (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Guerard, Albert J. (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Guerard, Albert L. (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Guggenheim, Mrs. Daniel (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Guggenhime, Richard E. (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Gunst, Morgan A. (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Gurley, John G. (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Guthrie, Anne (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Guthrie, Luell Weed (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Haas, Peter E. (Box 8, Folder 76)